//---Questions & Answers Bahasa Inggris Tes----//

const ques = [
    { 
        question : "At one o'clock, people usually have ....",
        opt1 : "lunch",
        opt2 : "dinner",
        opt3 : "breakfast",
        opt4 : "suffer",
        ans : "lunch"
    },
    { 
        question : "On school-day I have breakfast ....",
        opt1 : "at seven o'clock",
        opt2 : "at half past six",
        opt3 : "before half past six",
        opt4 : "at five",
        ans : "before half past six"
    },
    { 
        question : "Natasha got first rank in her class, she is very...",
        opt1 : "short",
        opt2 : "smart",
        opt3 : "bad",
        opt4 : "slim",
        ans : "smart"
    },
    { 
        question : "The following are the things on earth, except ...",
        opt1 : "Mountain",
        opt2 : "Waterfall",
        opt3 : "Comet",
        opt4 : "Lake",
        ans : "Comet"
    },
    { 
        question : "... rises in the morning.",
        opt1 : "Moon",
        opt2 : "Star",
        opt3 : "Planet",
        opt4 : "Sun",
        ans : "Sun"
    },
    { 
        question : "My stomach is sick. I have....",
        opt1 : "penicillin",
        opt2 : "headache",
        opt3 : "stomachache",
        opt4 : "a cold",
        ans : "stomachache"
    },
    { 
        question : "Andi : Let's go to library\nRini : Ok They want to....",
        opt1 : "reading books",
        opt2 : "listening music",
        opt3 : "playing football",
        opt4 : "watching the film",
        ans : "reading books"
    },
    { 
        question : "You can buy stationery in the ....",
        opt1 : "movie",
        opt2 : "mosque",
        opt3 : "bookstore",
        opt4 : "bank",
        ans : "bookstore"
    },
    { 
        question : "Mr. Hardi cures sick people in the hospital. He is a ....",
        opt1 : "farmer",
        opt2 : "doctor",
        opt3 : "teacher",
        opt4 : "driver",
        ans : "doctor"
    },
    { 
        question : "I read ... this morning.",
        opt1 : "video",
        opt2 : "a magazine",
        opt3 : "radio",
        opt4 : "a podcast",
        ans : "a magazine"
    }
]